[Music]
a hunk of hulk a burning fudge
it's a fictitious ice cream made famous
in
the avengers movies infinity war and
endgame
what is it who knows but we saw a clip
in one of them that it's actually a
green ice cream with little flecks of
we assume fudge it's not a real ice
cream we can't go out and buy it
so let's just do our take on it
let's see what we can come up with we've
decided to make a green
marshmallow base with fudge flecks a
fudge core
and a green crack top on and this is how
we'll do it
[Music]
for the base put all your ingredients in
a pan and then
chop up your 100 grams of marshmallows
add them to the mix and then
slowly heat it up until it's all
dissolved and fully incorporated
then chill in the fridge as you would do
normally
don't use these marshmallows that i've
used here and i'll explain why after
find a good marshmallow that's heavy
with vanilla flavor
[Music]
just put your condensed milk and your
chocolate into
a bain-marie heat that up nice and
slowly until it's all fully combined
then quite simply put it in the
container
put it in the fridge let it set and then
you can chop it up into whatever size
you need
this stuff will melt really really
quickly so make sure you
act fast and get it back in the freezer
as quick as you can we've taken some of
our fudge and kept it in the freezer
then we removed it and grated it in
preparation for the ice cream
five minutes to the end of the churn we
added the fudge flecks
into the ice cream itself ready for the
final stage
when your base is chilled take it out
and pop it in your machine
five minutes from the end of the churn
pop those frozen fudge flecks
in to distribute them
to make the fudge core melt your
chocolate and butter i've done it in the
microwave but you can do over
over a hob if you like once that's
melted
whisk up your egg and sugar and then
combine the two
whisk it together really quickly and
then finally add a little bit of glucose
to it
as that will help stop it freezing hard
[Music]
to do the core we've put a plastic tube
sealed at the bottom
inside the ice cream popped in the
freezer for 10-15 minutes something like
that
when ready we've removed the core and
poured in our fudge
for the chocolate top you're actually
going to make a water ganache
now with white chocolate that's a six to
one ratio normally
but to make sure you get a nice crack do
this one at 12 to 1
12 parts chocolate one part water pop it
in the microwave until it's all melted
add your green coloring and away you go
i did this one in the video wrong
had to redo it at that 12 to 1 ratio
pop that back in the freezer until
you're ready to eat it
[Music]
the name for this ice cream obviously
comes from an elvis presley song hung
hunger burning love
i just wonder if elvis would have been
as popular if we sang about a hunk of
hulk burning fudge
without it but i mean look at that tub
if that isn't one of the best tubs what
i've done then i don't know what it is
it's amazing she's honestly she's
getting better as time goes on
should we uh open up see what it looks
like
[Music]
i mean
the chocolate top green obviously
it's hulk so how would
how would hulk get through that well i
think we all know
first things first the fudge core
i mean look at it it's proper fudgy
you can scoop it straight out the tub
recipe for that is below i'm using that
again
the ice cream we went for marshmallow
this time
don't use those marshmallows i've put in
there they've got no flavor whatsoever
marshmallows have a lot of gelatin so it
turns much
different to your normal non-gelatin ice
cream
i remade this one with a different
marshmallow just a
home store brand marshmallow much better
consistency much better stronger flavor
so
choose your marshmallows carefully how
does it taste
we've got some of that chocolate top
it's white chocolate colored green
it all just comes together you're free
to make these flavors whatever you want
fruit make any ice cream however
but i went for marshmallow marshmallow
chocolate
those little fudge flecks in there it's
great
really good combination it's a lot of
fun making this one
and my nice handmade japanese bowl
let me know what you do different if
you'd make this fictitious ice cream
flavor
in a different way different combo
pistachio maybe something like that then
let us know you know let us know down in
the comments what flavors you'd go for
anyway hope you enjoyed this hunger
hulker burning fudge
ice cream recreation and
if you enjoy watching us make ice cream
make sure you like and subscribe
and we'll see you next week on the next
video